

An Information Security Analyst with seven years of professional experience, specializing in cloud security, project management, and technology implementations. A proven track record of coordinating with technical teams and third-party agencies to perform comprehensive security audits and achieve compliance with industry regulations and security standards.

Professional Experience

Information Security Analyst

Ad vanced Sec u ri ty Co nsu Ita nts, N ew York, NY J u ly 2016 - Present

- Deliver information security consulting services to client accounts valued at \$600K-\$1.3M, conduct vulnerability assessments and security audits of existing protocols, and interface with internal teamsand client IT groups to refine security controlsand policies
- Develop access management protocols and implement 2-factor authentication to ensure secure access across 500K users for an enterprise customer account
- Create strategy and plans for the implementation of cloud security technology and the migration from outdated legacy systems

Information Security Analyst

Brooklyn IT Consultants, New York, NY May 2011 - July 2016

- Coo rd i n ated wi th the Sen i or Security Advisor to d e I iver IT co nsu Iti ng se rvices to
 0+ client businesses and ensure customer success, including penetration testing, disaster recovery planning, and security audits
- Developed and implemented security controls and technology solutions to aid clients in obtaining compliance with industry requirements, including PCI, ISO 27001, and SOX

123 Your Street, New York. NY 12345 j osera m i rez@exam ple.com (123) 456-7890

Education

Bachelor of Science (B.S,) Computer Science

University of Syracuse, Syracuse, CA Septem be r 2007 - May 2011

Key Skills

- ♦ Information Security
- Penetration Testing
- Access Management
- ♦ User Authentication
- ♦ Technology Implementation

Certifications

- Certified Information Security
 Manager (CISM) 2017
- Certifi ed I nformati on System s Auditor (CISA), 2016
- Certifi ed I nformati on System s
 Security Professional (CISSP), 2016
- CompTIA Security*, 2013
- CompTIA Network*, 2011